A Guide to the Micajah Woods Letter Books
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #1444
Micajah Woods Letter Books 1874-1902
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
1444
17 bound volumes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1942 May 29
Container List
- 1874 Jul 17 -1875 Oct 30 (Box Box 1)
- 1878 Aug 3 -1879 Apr 4 (Box Box 1)
- 1882 Apr -Dec 20 (Box Box 1)
- 1882 Dec 21 -1883 Aug 18 (Box Box 1)
- 1883 Aug 18 -1884 May 29 (Box Box 2)
- 1885 Jun 22 -1886 Aug 19 (Box Box 2)
- 1887Aug 30 -1888 Jun 22 (Box Box 2)
- 1888 Jun 26 -1889 Feb 27 (Box Box 2)
- 1889 Feb 17 -Dec 18 (Box Box 3)
- 1892 Jan 1 -Jul 25 (Box Box 3)
- 1892 Ju1 25 -Dec 27 (Box Box 3)
- 1893 Jun 10 -Sep 16 (Box Box 3)
- 1895 Jan 23 -Sep 2 (Box Box 3)
- 1896 Jul 20 -1897 May 1 (Box Box 4)
- 1898 Jun 13 -Nov 18 (Box Box 4)
- 1898 Nov 18 -1899 Mar 9 (Box Box 4)
- 1901 Nov 29 -1902 Jul 2 (Box Box 4)